(The event venue in Dongdaemun where My Star is waiting)
(It's packed with reporters.)
(This is the press conference for "The Scandal.")
(He's handling his schedule without the secretaries.)
(Ji Chang Wook, today's My Star)
(The actress joining him for the event is Son Ye Jin.)
(Actress Nana is also here!)
(My Star summoned the secretaries for this important occasion.)
Well...
This is...
my second time.
This is my second time.
So I've gotten closer to them.
We've built a bond.
- Is this okay?
- What?
(Last November, Chang Wook appeared on the show as My Star.)
You can drive if this is uncomfortable for you, Chang Wook.
(When he suggested going to a bakery)
It's near Gangnam-gu Office.
- Gosh, that's too far.
- That's too far.
- Sorry?
- Is Gangnam-gu Office...
- Are you perplexed?
We're running late...
because of the traffic jam.
(They were even late.)
Did I...
get to do anything...
I wanted to do today?
(My Star has been through a tough experience.)
(Worked up)
We got closer...
and built a bond.
I'm sure we'll have better teamwork this time.
That's what I'm expecting.
And today,
we have a press conference.
It's a public event,
so I'm sure...
they'll behave appropriately...
for the occasion.
(A sound effect worthy of a global streaming platform)
(Staggering)
Why did you get out like that?
(Anyone would think he's a local cab driver.)
Why did you leave your buttons undone?
(He shamelessly uses someone else's vehicle.)
It's hot. Let's go somewhere in the shade.
It's hot.
It'll burn my skin.
(The sun seems to feel especially hot to Driver Kim.)
(His soulmate arrives shortly afterward.)
Hi.
I thought you were a manager or something.
(I thought you were a manager or something.)
Welcome, Young Master.
(His dimples show when he sees his older bestie's outfit.)
You said you wouldn't wear a blazer. Why are you wearing it?
(Seo Jin is wearing a neat suit.)
You said you wouldn't wear it, but here you are.
I knew it.
(The two men in suits enter the venue.)
(Dashing)
This way?
Is the global streaming service hosting this event?
Yes.
(If so...)
(He quickly checks his appearance...)
(to make sure he looks good on a global stage.)
(He's even wearing a name tag from the global OTT platform.)
You guys look like agents.
Hello.
(They head over to meet My Star, looking classy.)
Is he the manager we saw last time?
- I don't know.
- Maybe not?
You must be his new manager.
- No, we met last time.
- Are you the same manager?
- Yes.
- Why do you look different today?
- Right. It's the suit.
- Please take a seat here.
- Hello.
(They met the manager last season.)
(1 year ago, now)
(His style has changed quite a lot since they last saw him.)
- Are you the same manager?
- Yes.
Why do you look different today?
Right. It's the suit.
- Please take a seat here.
- Here?
You look like a different person.
Today is the press conference...
for the OTT original series "The Scandal."
This is his second time appearing on My Genie Secretary.
Please take good care of him.
It'll be released on September 18.
It's nice to meet you.
It sounds like you memorized those lines.
Yes, I did.
(He got caught.)
I suggested...
you wear suits.
- Was that you?
- Yes.
(I didn't need to wear a suit after all.)
You looked better in the outfit...
- you wore last time.
- Right.
- You look awkward.
- Yes.
(They tease him right away since they've met before.)
You look like you're wearing someone else's clothes.
- You can't even button it.
- Hey.
That button is about to pop off.
Try buttoning it.
- This is...
- Did you try to lose weight or...
(It's just cruel to the button.)
That button might hit us in the eye.
(Their antics get him dizzy.)
I'll tell Chang Wook...
- to buy you a suit.
- No, it's okay.
Don't take it too far.
(Laughing)
This is today's schedule and the company card.
Please take a look.
Please brief him...
on today's schedule when you meet him.
(My Star's Schedule, Time: 9:30am to 5pm, Location: Press Conference)
(His schedule is packed...)
(with promotional events until the evening.)
(The project he'll be presenting this time is...)
Actually, I have a favour to ask...
(For My Star's impressive acting...)
A favour?
(and the cast's transformations, it's already been making headlines.)
(The most highly anticipated release of the second half of the year)
(The temptation of three people who dare to cross the line)
("The Scandal")
(This time, he's back as the greatest ladies' man in Joseon.)
Are they doing an interview?
- Yes.
- Is it live?
They're in an interview with an international media outlet.
(They're doing a video interview...)
(with an international media outlet in the room right next door.)
It's not morning in South America right now.
It must be evening there.
(The actors are connecting with audiences around the world.)
No one is entirely innocent, and every character is in the gray area.
I'd like you to defend your characters.
I'm not sure. How should I defend him?
He loved them.
(Laughing)
Love isn't a crime, is it?
(My Star lightens the mood with a playful remark.)
Actually, there's nothing else I can say...
to defend him.
The press conference will be starting again shortly.
As you both know,
please keep an eye on the articles and comments on online communities.
- Search his name online.
- That's...
And since he'll be using his voice a lot today,
- make sure he has...
- There's a tumbler.
Yes. This tumbler and the things we prepared for him.
Isn't it the same tumbler from last time?
- It is.
- I forgot to take it.
- You left it behind.
- Yes.
(This tumbler is...)
- Thank you, Kwang Kyu.
- I forgot to take it.
Please be mindful.
(A careful request)
I'll be more mindful. Gosh, there's a mosquito.
- My apologies.
- No, it's fine.
I'm sorry. It was my fault.
But he's not going anywhere today.
- He will after it's over.
- He'll stay in the same venue.
These are good for his throat.
- And...
- What are good for his throat?
Honey and effervescent vitamin tablets.
I put these in the bag.
I'd appreciate it if you put them in his tumbler.
I put everything he needs in the bag.
My goodness.
(He couldn't wait and is already sucking on some honey.)
Please take good care of our staff members too.
Make sure to check on the other actors' managers...
Can we go to a buffet and pay with this card?
- Do you want to go to a buffet?
- Yes.
(He has a feeling their aftercare service is going to fail too.)
Please make sure Chang Wook gets to do whatever he wants.
When has he ever not gotten to do what he wants?
(His Genie secretaries will do anything this time.)
(Meanwhile, in the interview room)
(My Star is in the middle of an interview.)
The characters' good and evil sides aren't clearly defined.
(Staring)
Did she leave that one strand of hair out on purpose?
(A strand of hair is bothering Seo Jin.)
(His eyes are fixed on someone's hair instead of My Star.)
This is what managers do.
- You should do that too.
- What?
Why? That looks wrong.
- Is that wrong?
- I want to fix it.
You're Chang Wook's manager, but you're more interested in her.
He'll take care of himself.
(I also left a few strands of my hair down.)
(Another secretary is distracted as well.)
I've briefly worked with all of those actors.
- Do you know them all then?
- Of course.
What project did you work on with Ye Jin?
A drama called "Blood and Ties."
- Isn't it a movie? Is it a drama?
- It's a movie.
You said it was a drama.
Were you in the same scene as her?
Yes, I was.
- So you worked with everyone.
- Right.
Did you work with Nana as well?
There was a drama called "Genesis,"
which was cancelled halfway through.
(He met Nana through a drama.)
(Kwang Kyu has worked with all three actors before.)
I'm curious.
Will Nana recognise me?
She would know who you are,
but I'm not sure if she remembers working with you.
Is that what you want to know?
Because we only worked together briefly.
She might not remember then.
- Were you in the same scene as her?
- What?
- Of course.
When I fell,
she helped me up.
She was so kind.
(Kwang Kyu has fond memories of her.)
(Looking at Nana only)
Thank you.
(The interview is over.)
(My Star leaves first.)
Chang Wook.
(Spotting the secretaries)
Why do you keep calling us?
(They finally met My Star.)
- Did you want to meet us again?
- Yes.
- I missed you guys so much.
- Gosh.
- Your suit is amazing.
- Sorry?
- Let me change...
- Sure.
- my pants.
(My Star is getting changed.)
(Nana leaves the interview room.)
Hi.
(That's Nana's voice.)
(Does she remember him?)
Nana.
(Nana)
- Hello.
Do you remember me?
- Of course, I do.
- You do?
You know the drama aired, right?
- It aired.
- I didn't know.
I didn't even get paid.
I only found out about it recently.
(He's a lot happier to see Nana than My Star.)
- Weren't you hurt at the time?
- No, I wasn't.
You weren't?
It was cancelled halfway through.
- Right?
- So I quit.
You look better now.
You look much better than before.
You too.
- I'm counting on you today.
- Please move.
- What are you filming today?
- My Genie Secretary.
(It seems he didn't forget his duty.)
- I'm counting on you.
- Sure.
But you aren't my secretary, are you?
We're secretaries for everyone.
(We're secretaries for everyone.)
Everyone is My Star today.
- You know who Seo Jin is, right?
- Yes.
- Last time...
- We met at a restaurant once.
- We did.
- At a restaurant?
- You remember everything.
- Thanks for paying for us.
What? Did you pay for her meal?
Including her fans, there were a dozen of people.
There were?
He's always happy to treat people to a meal.
- You may go in.
- Okay. Good luck.
- Is this the one?
- This is her waiting room.
(They don't even know where My Star's waiting room is.)
(Ye Jin's waiting room is right next door.)
(Roaming around for no reason)
- Hello.
(His dimples show.)
Here comes a pretty girl.
(Here comes a pretty girl.)
- Hello.
- Right?
(The reason he calls her "a pretty girl")
(Who always treats you to meals)
(The girl)
(The pretty girl who always treats you to meals)
(Who is it? Who is the female lead?)
(Son Ye Jin)
(She's pretty indeed.)
(Acknowledging)
(Even Seo Jin, the Thinker, admitted she was beautiful.)
(Here comes a pretty girl.)
(Looking intently)
She's the prettiest.
"She's the prettiest."
(According to Seo Jin, she's the prettiest girl.)
(My Star they forgot about for a moment is here.)
- I thought you'd get changed.
- Yes.
- I changed my pants.
- You did?
My pants were wrinkled, so they ironed them.
(He stands with his hands behind his back, gazing into the distance.)
Have you been doing well?
Yes. How about you?
It seems you lost weight.
- Me?
- Yes.
(Unlike earlier, he doesn't look enthusiastic at all.)
- Haven't you been eating much?
- Well...
(Laughing)
Why are you laughing? What's the problem?
I like it.
My goodness.
It's not easy to appear on our show twice.
I guess we were too nice to him last time.
I think we were too nice to him last time.
Did I get to do anything I wanted to do today?
(Don't forget the humiliation you suffered last year.)
(My Star's Schedule)
(11am, Press conference for "The Scandal")
(Today is the press conference...)
(where "The Scandal" will finally be unveiled.)
(A total of 124 reporters are in attendance.)
(A question-and-answer session with the director and cast)
(It's also livestreamed globally.)
(My Star's main schedule)
("The Scandal," Press Conference)
What do you want to do today?
- Is there anything you want to do?
- Me?
- Yes.
- First off,
I want to get through this schedule smoothly.
Yes. Do whatever you want.
(Laughing)
You know we always go along with you and let you do what you want.
- Is that so?
- Of course.
- Last time...
- We did that last time.
We let you do anything you wanted to do.
- We always catered to you.
- We absolutely did.
Last time, I thought about it at the end.
I didn't get to do anything I wanted.
That's not true.
- So today...
- Did you prepare something?
(Look forward to it.)
(They'll make My Star laugh.)
(A day where he gets to do everything he wants)
(The secretaries will take good care of him.)
(I haven't felt this for a while.)
(Getting tired from having fun.)
Manager, could I have some coffee?
(In a rush)
- Here it is.
- I saw another tumbler earlier.
- What was that?
- I carry two tumblers.
Where did it go?
What's that for? Yes, that one.
- It has coffee in it.
- Coffee?
- So it's the same?
- Yes. I usually...
Hello.
- Hello.
- It's been a long time.
- Yes.
- Hello.
(Jung Ji Woo, the director of "The Scandal")
You look younger.
- I know.
- Why do you look younger?
Kyung Rim.
Oh, my. Kyung Rim.
(Park Kyung Rim, press conference host)
- Hello.
- Oh, my.
Hello.
- Are you going to a wedding?
- Yes, I am.
Why are you dressed up so nicely?
Oh, my. Ye Jin.
(Ye Jin came to say hi to Kyung Rim.)
Oh, my goodness.
(Gosh, it's Son Ye Jin.)
Is Kyung Rim older than her?
What kind of nonsense is that?
(He went too far with a joke when the pretty girl appeared.)
- Have you been doing well?
- Yes.
He's my manager today.
- Is that so?
- I'm his secretary.
Who's the manager?
I'm the manager.
He's my secretary who's working for me.
(Manager, manager's secretary, My Star)
- Is he your secretary?
- Yes, he's my secretary.
(He's still working as a subcontractor for a subcontractor.)
- By the way, - Yes.
- could you...
- Yes.
- take some photos of me...
- Okay.
- with this film camera...
- Don't you think it's a waste?
from time to time?
Sure, I will.
- Let me take a photo.
- Okay.
Yes.
Just take the photos as naturally as possible.
Wait. This feels totally unnatural.
(The photographer is obviously taking a photo.)
Look here.
One, two...
(Laughing)
In 1, 2, 3.
Okay.
Three.
(Unnatural)
- Just take them naturally.
- Why don't you stand together?
Why don't you stand together?
That's not what he asked.
He didn't tell you to take a photo of his manager.
Take photos with him.
- Stand together.
- Why are you acting like this?
This is our second time.
No. Don't take photos like this.
If you take some good photos, I'll get them developed,
post them on Instagram,
- and use them as content.
- Please listen to him.
(Sorry)
I guess I'll struggle today just like I did last time.
- Yes.
(Sneaking)
(Why did My Star suddenly burst into laughter?)
Kyung Rim, can I take a photo of you?
- Sure.
- Both of you.
(He turned his back on My Star and headed toward Ye Jin.)
In 1, 2, 3.
(It looks like he's taking a photo at a wedding hall.)
Is it taken?
Do secretaries take photos too?
- Yes.
- We do anything they want.
Really?
Are you going to pick up the developed photos later?
I guess they will.
Chang Wook will get them developed.
The flash didn't go off.
("I Came to a Press Conference." Photo by Kwang Kyu)
Did you actually ride the horse?
- Yes.
- You did an amazing job.
We filmed all the horseback-riding scenes...
- in one day. It was exhausting.
- Really?
It surprised me. You have amazing horseback-riding skills.
I spent the whole day riding horses.
Is there anything else that surprised you?
Anything else?
(Laughing)
It was full of surprises.
(She's pretty and funny.)
My gosh.
You look good...
- with those broad shoulders.
- How come you look younger now?
- What are you talking about?
- How?
You look a lot younger.
You look much younger than before.
- We haven't met for a long time.
- Right.
- With Park Hae Il, right?
- Yes.
Yes, you're right.
- Do you remember me?
- Of course, I do.
Do you remember "Modern Boy?"
- "Modern Boy."
- Of course.
How have you been?
I've been doing variety shows.
I see.
When I was a rookie actor,
I auditioned for his movie.
Which one?
(Chang Wook joins them.)
What was it?
(My Star joins them, but they barely pay him any attention.)
- "Happy End."
So did you audition...
- for the role Joo Jin Mo played?
- Yes.
And I got rejected.
This is awkward.
(They're still talking with the director.)
The press conference.
(Oh, right!)
(He finally saw My Star.)
Please keep a close eye on it.
- Sure.
- I'm quite sensitive today.
Please keep a close eye on me.
Okay, I will.
(Please pay attention to me as well.)
(Just as My Star was getting a little sensitive,)
(the press conference for "The Scandal" began.)
(The press is buzzing with excitement.)
I'm Kyung Rim from the Park family,
and I'll be hosting today's press conference for "The Scandal."
It's nice to meet you.
"The Scandal" is...
I don't usually get nervous, but I feel nervous now.
(The actors feel nervous as well.)
Let me walk you through the order of events.
Nana, I'll show you.
(Is Seo Jin looking at something else?)
(Is he looking at the pretty girl?)
(Kwang Kyu is peeking as well.)
(Tapping)
- Say hi to her.
- We said hi earlier.
- You did?
- Yes.
I'm quite sensitive.
(Are they not paying attention again?)
(Glancing at Seo Jin)
(Glancing at Ye Jin)
(My Star wants the secretaries' attention.)
(Oh, right.)
How is Kyung Soo doing?
- Kyung Soo? I haven't seen him...
- You haven't seen him?
- for a very long time. Yes.
- Is that so?
You work all the time. How are you supposed to meet anyone?
- I know.
- Right?
We saw Kyung Soo last time. I guess that was the last time he saw him.
Really?
You were promoting together.
You're right.
After it aired,
I started shooting another drama.
So I haven't seen him for a very long time.
These days,
I haven't met anyone.
When work is over,
- You need to rest.
- I'm too busy resting at home.
I either work or stay at home.
I've lost touch with everyone.
- I've become a bit of a loner.
- Yes.
(Ji Chang Wook, 39 years old, My Star, a loner)
- It's because you always work.
- Yes.
No one calls me anymore.
(Teary-eyed)
When you take on a year-long project,
your social life basically comes to an end.
That's so true.
It's embarrassing now.
Why?
If someone calls...
- And they ask you to meet up?
- and asks to meet up,
I feel bad having to turn them down...
- because I have a shoot.
- Is it easier...
- if they don't call you at all?
- Yes.
That's why I didn't contact you. I didn't want you to feel bad.
(That's a lame excuse.)
- But we met today.
- Yes.
- This is the best way to meet up.
We'll begin today's press conference for "The Scandal..."
with a photo call.
Please welcome Nana to the stage, who plays Hui Yeon.
(The photo call begins with Nana.)
Nana takes on her first historical drama...
with "The Scandal," making a new transformation.
Please look forward to it...
(Despite saying she's nervous, she poses with ease.)
and show her lots of love.
- Mr. Ji.
- Yes.
Please go on stage when Nana comes down.
Show her lots of love.
Please stand here.
(Holding hands)
(My Star is a little nervous.)
Has it already been this long?
- I know.
- Gosh.
- Look toward the center.
- My gosh.
(Seo Jin is watching My Star who feels nervous.)
We filmed the drama in the middle of summer last year.
(Actually, he's watching Ye Jin.)
You don't have to look in the mirror. You look pretty.
You look pretty. Stop looking in the mirror.
- Why do you say that?
- It's because you look pretty.
(He successfully grabbed her attention.)
(His dimples deepen.)
I mean...
Do you want some honey?
(Do you want some honey?)
- I'm fine.
- Honey? It's good for your throat.
If I eat honey now,
my mouth might feel sticky during the press conference.
Is that so?
It surprised me...
when he talked to Ye Jin.
He doesn't usually do that.
She kept coughing. That's why.
(A lame excuse)
She looked fine to me.
She kept coughing.
She kept coughing next to me.
We'll check the footage.
Go on. I talked to her because she kept coughing.
(We checked the footage, and she didn't cough.)
How about a strand of hair you were talking about?
- I think she did that on purpose.
- I did that on purpose.
(I left that on purpose.)
(I see.)
Okay.
(They leave My Star to his nerves...)
(and keep chatting.)
Why are you so good at golf?
- Excuse me?
- You're good at golf.
- You saw the YouTube video?
- Yes.
I practised.
You're quite good.
Do you shoot in the 80s?
(No)
- No.
- You shoot in the 100s, right?
I do.
You're good.
I just have good form.
Your form looks good.
Is your husband still a single-digit handicap?
- Yes.
- Is he?
- He hasn't played golf for a while.
- Is that so?
But he's good.
- That's what I heard.
- He's good.
I heard it from his friends that he's good...
because they are my juniors.
Some of her husband's friends...
are my juniors.
Ye Jin is good at golf. I saw her video on YouTube.
That's why I asked.
Have you watched Chang Wook's video on YouTube recently?
Was he on YouTube?
(He had no idea.)
Thank you. I'll see you later.
(Glancing)
Please go back the way you came.
Please welcome Ji Chang Wook who played Cho Won.
He'll show a new side of himself...
as Joseon's greatest ladies' man in "The Scandal."
Everyone looks amazing today.
(Charismatic)
Yes. You're Joseon's greatest ladies' man.
Can you show us a heart?
That's what I'm talking about.
Look to your left.
Why does he never stop working?
- Who?
- Chang Wook.
All right. Great.
The crew has perfect teamwork.
Let's wrap up the photo call.
Thank you.
(A short break before the question-and-answer session)
(Picking up)
(Kwang Kyu goes straight to My Star to give him a tumbler.)
(Thank you.)
(He even fans him with a portable fan.)
How come this is so strong?
It's not a portable fan. It's an air gun.
(An air gun for My Star)
It sounds like an airplane.
I place it here when it gets hot.
(Demonstrating)
It's really strong.
- There's such a thing?
- It's an air gun.
It's like a hair dryer.
It's no joke.
(The 56.5-year-old secretaries discovered modern technology.)
(Wandering around)
(Kwang Kyu heads somewhere with the air gun.)
(He sits next to Nana instead of My Star.)
- Right here.
- Right there. Goodness.
- At the back.
- It's been a while, Nana.
It's been a while, Nana.
- What is he doing?
- Ji Chang Wook.
(Read the room, Kwang Kyu.)
(Unaware of the tension, he's busy taking care of Nana.)
I know, right? It's been a long while.
- I'll head out.
- Okay.
My Star.
(She's even taken the title of "My Star.")
Did you know that they kept wandering...
around Son Ye Jin and Nana?
(Exclaiming)
(Worried look)
Actually,
I knew that...
they weren't next to me.
(I know very well that they weren't next to me.)
I'll head out.
(I'll head out.)
(Putting aside his disappointment, he heads into the press conference.)
We'll invite them to the stage.
(My Star gets on the stage first.)
I think it's because of their fancy clothes.
The stage feels like a runway.
Can we enter?
(The secretaries stand by next to the stage.)
Hello, I'm Ji Chang Wook, playing the role of Cho Won.
Nice to meet you.
(Taking a picture of him before he misses it)
(Making sure to zoom in)
Get one on film.
(My Star's request)
(Complying)
- Make sure they all appear.
- I thought it was interesting.
- All of them?
- And...
- Does the title show up as well?
- the work with the director...
- Yes.
- I'm excited to work with him.
You should take it.
- All right.
- You should take it.
This is blocking it. Go inside a bit.
- A bit to the back.
- What should viewers expect...
- to see in this drama?
- Don't show your face.
(Pushing the older bestie for the perfect shot)
(A top photographer at heart)
(My Star turns toward Kwang Kyu.)
- Did you take it?
- Yes.
Chang Wook looked this way just now.
- Did you miss that?
- I didn't get that.
(Goodness)
What charm does "Cho Won" played by Ji Chang Wook have?
He shows his fashionista side...
Oh, the fashionista in Joseon?
(He seemed nervous, but he's doing great.)
- Look up some articles...
- From now on,
- about Chang Wook.
- let's find out the secret...
(He should just do it himself.)
(Checking his latest news articles in real time)
(Nana)
(Nana again)
(Nana once again)
I told you to look up Chang Wook's articles.
Why are you looking at Nana's pictures only?
I'm not.
Seriously.
I was looking at all the pictures.
I looked at all of them.
(Kwang Kyu's honorary My Star Nana)
(He's looking up his real My Star's articles.)
(He found something.)
This is what the article says.
(What is it?)
(Look at this.)
(Bursting into laughter)
This...
Where is this journalist?
Who wrote this?
It's Son Ye Jin and Hyun Bin.
What are we going to do about this?
(Son Ye Jin, Hyun Bin, and Nana)
They wrote Hyun Bin instead of Ji Chang Wook.
(They got the wrong name.)
It must have happened because they're just rushing things here.
(But...)
This journalist...
keeps writing Hyun Bin's name.
(Multiple headlines went up with errors.)
Where is this journalist?
(A new task came up. Find the journalist...)
Look for the journalist.
(and get the headlines corrected.)
(There are 124 attendees. It's like finding a needle in a haystack.)
There are too many people.
How are we going to find this person?
(Overcoming the poor eyesight, he scans with eagle eyes.)
Isn't it that person?
The person in the middle wearing black glasses.
- Wearing a hat?
- There.
Go there.
I don't know.
Is there anyone with the final questions?
We have to hurry. It's the last question.
(It's time for the last question.)
Where is it?
(He heads out first.)
Where should I go?
Go through there.
(He needs to find the journalist before the press conference ends!)
(A desperate dash...)
(by 58-year-old Kwang Kyu, all for My Star)
- Are you a journalist from...
- No.
No?
- No?
- He's over there.
It's not him.
(Live updates)
(A flustered back)
- Where is he?
- The person wearing a hat.
- Over there?
- Yes.
(A golden tip from another journalist)
(He's on his way to meet you.)
(Kwang Kyu)
I saw him.
Actually,
there wasn't anyone walking around there.
But someone kept moving around.
I wondered, "What is he doing?"
(What is he doing?)
"What's happening? What is he doing?"
(He finally meets the journalist who wrote Hyun Bin.)
(Showing him)
Hyun Bin...
- I'll correct them.
- Right.
(Kwang Kyu successfully requests the correction of the articles.)
(Crouching)
(The rough road back after completing the mission)
(Falling)
It wouldn't be nice to draw attention to myself.
I didn't want to cause inconvenience to anyone.
I quietly waddled out.
But you drew attention.
I did?
(I did?)
(Laughing)
(He reaches the final obstacle, the line of cameras.)
It was like going through barbed wire in my military days.
(Panting)
(I made it!)
My joints are hurting everywhere.
I can't rotate it.
(The correction of the article cost him his joints.)
You did a great job.
- I did a great job, right?
- You did.
- Then...
- It would have been trouble.
Can I go home now?
- I'll go home. You carry on.
- No.
It was nice meeting you.
(My Star's press conference ended well...)
(after the correction of the article.)
(Sighing)
(He's still exhausted.)
Great job.
(Great job)
Well done.
Great work.
(Great job)
I could see you so well.
(I could see you so well.)
I'm going...
Do you normally...
watch from the side?
- Of course.
- I was touched...
because they kept watching from start to finish.
We're his managers.
(Showing off nonstop)
(His hands are free.)
- Where did I put the bag?
- That's why...
- Hold on.
- The bag.
(Exclaiming)
Don't worry about him.
How can I not worry about him?
Your bag.
Where did I put your bag?
The bag is missing again.
(The case of My Star's missing bag after his missing tumbler)
Quickly head back.
I'll go and look for the bag.
Were we on the first floor?
- L1 level.
Goodness.
Just when I thought everything was perfect...
(No wonder things were going so smoothly.)
There it is.
(There it is.)
(He found the bag.)
(He found the journalist and the bag.)
I did my part.
(Heading back to My Star)
(Chang Wook got changed.)
- You should eat.
You should eat first.
Don't worry about us.
Is this your seat?
Is it this one?
(My Star's Schedule: 12pm, Lunch time)
You should eat.
Okay.
(My Star's brief break...)
(in between a packed schedule of photo ops and interviews)
Goodness.
Is it...
Is it your first press conference of the year?
Me?
Is this my first one this year?
- There was "Colony."
- There was another one, right?
Yes. There was "Colony."
Right.
(3 projects released this year alone.)
That's right.
You did three press conferences in a year?
Me? I kept...
I've worked on a lot of projects.
I did that because...
I think I've been going through...
that period lately.
A period where I want to do many things.
I want to do more things.
You worked with us last October, right?
- That's right.
- Right?
That was a drama called "The Manipulated..."
which I worked on with Kyung Soo.
He found it.
(Clapping)
- Would you like coffee?
- Thank you.
Have something to eat.
Lunch?
Is our lunch here?
He's...
(A simple man who lights up at the word "food.")
Goodness.
First...
During the press conference earlier,
Yes.
Kwang Kyu kept moving around at the very front.
- Yes.
- So...
Seo Jin was watching from the side.
It was reassuring.
How did I do today?
Today...
Overall, I think everything went smoothly...
and without any issues.
- What kind of...
- What?
(In what way were there no issues?)
There was an issue!
There was an issue...
What kind of issue was it?
Instead of Ji Chang Wook, the world star,
- Yes.
- they kept using Hyun Bin's name.
- They kept posting such articles.
- Because of Son Ye Jin.
For example, it went like this.
("The Scandal," starring Son Ye Jin, Hyun Bin, and Nana, is a romance?)
Like that.
- We found the journalist...
- Yes.
and asked for a correction.
That was why he came in...
and talked to that person.
- Right.
- You saw that?
Someone kept walking around,
so I looked at him. It was Kwang Kyu...
talking to a journalist about something.
So I was wondering what it was about.
I had no idea it would be about that. I'm so grateful.
- We took care of it smoothly.
- Thank you.
He kept getting your name wrong...
in many articles.
(Let's eat now.)
- Let's eat.
- Thank you for the food.
Today...
(He only gets 50 minutes to eat.)
What will I be doing after lunch?
After lunch?
You have an interview.
An interview.
(Seo Jin already memorized the schedule.)
But...
(But...)
working from 9am to 6pm is a bit...
Are other press conferences like this too?
Yes.
Since there aren't many chances to gather up like this,
we keep doing interviews when we can gather them.
I've never seen one that's so long.
(It would be really tiresome.)
You kept wandering around Son Ye Jin...
and Nana.
Who?
What are you talking about?
I kept taking pictures of you.
You took the fan to Nana.
You took a water bottle to Ye Jin.
- What?
- Honey?
He gave her honey? Who?
- You gave it to her.
- My honey?
That's right.
I didn't give her the honey. It was Seo Jin.
No.
(My Star's mood is starting to drop.)
I didn't give it to her.
This is how it feels.
She asked for one and I didn't give her.
I don't mind them...
giving my things to others...
because they do that in good will.
It's fine since she needs it.
But I'm a bit disappointed because they didn't do...
any of that for me.
(They didn't do any of that for me.)
(This is bad.)
It was in the bag.
I didn't give it to her when she asked for one.
(Ye Jin asked for it, but he didn't give her.)
(I asked for it?)
- Hey.
- Yes?
How did she know you had honey?
Ye Jin didn't want it, but you kept insisting.
What are you talking about? She asked for it and I refused.
- Ye Jin asked for it?
- She knew there was honey.
How did she know I had honey?
I guess she knows that you normally carry honey.
I'm getting confused since he's so confident.
- No way.
- I didn't give it to her.
You gave it to her.
- I didn't.
- Goodness.
Where is it?
You did offer her.
I didn't offer her. I just said, "There's honey. Do you want one?"
That's what...
- This...
- Let's check the tapes.
Let's check the tapes.
How much will you bet?
- What?
- I can bet my whole fortune.
(He's scared.)
- That's big.
- How much do you have?
Bet all of it.
I didn't even know there was honey.
(He's never even seen the honey.)
Even if I keep feeling hurt,
(My Star isn't getting anything out of it.)
they're not going to give me honey.
Is there really honey?
(Let me see it.)
My Star.
(The honey his real manager packed for him)
Have some honey.
(Getting honey before Chuseok just because he asked)
It's really not nice.
(The secretaries who enjoyed the honey are not nice.)
I said that when you were holding the fan.
How would you know that?
That's why...
So that's why you went to Nana...
and told her you should have a meal together sometime.
Kwang Kyu...
(Did you see that?)
He didn't ask me that.
I mean...
(Please explain that.)
When did you ask to grab a meal? This month?
No.
- Were you trying to make plans?
- No.
I asked her if she'd like to join us...
and Ji Chang Wook for a packed lunch.
She seemed to have plans.
You were rejected?
(That's what we call being rejected.)
(Facing the reality he tried to ignore)
- I thought we'd eat with Nana.
- Charge that fan.
It feels like it wouldn't work because you used it so much.
It works.
- This...
- You used it on Nana...
for like 30 minutes.
(Crying)
It's not strong enough.
(The air gun is still alive.)
Even his fan is different because he's a global actor.
Was this given to you as a gift?
No. I bought it.
Ji Hyun...
Her manager...
Who's Ji Hyun?
Jun Ji Hyun.
Your favourite Jun Ji Hyun.
Jun Ji Hyun?
Of course.
- Did you ever work with her?
- Of course.
We worked on "Windstruck" together.
(A character who gets overpowered by Jun Ji Hyun)
I remember getting slapped by Jun Ji Hyun.
(They were close enough that he even got slapped by her.)
Then when we're promoting "HumanXGumiho..."
He'll be working on a drama with Jun Ji Hyun.
- He is currently working on it.
- You are?
- Yes.
- He's working on it.
It will be released next year.
- We have to promote that.
- Right.
Let's have Chang Wook as a permanent member.
As a promotion day.
You'll always be with us on promotion days.
(Sighing)
I wasn't sighing because of that.
That's not what I meant. These days,
I have so many things to do that I just sigh without realising.
- Yes.
- Try to work a little less.
I'm thinking of leaving behind the honey next time.
(We'll give you honey when you come, Jun Ji Hyun.)
How many months did you work on this?
(Back to talking about the drama)
It's been more than six months.
That was a long shoot.
(My Star filmed over 6 months.)
Even with the post-production...
The director is quite meticulous,
so he must have worked a lot on the post-production.
- We re-recorded the dialogue...
- See?
for almost 20 hours.
(Nearly 20 hours per actor)
Just to re-record the dialogue.
That would have been everything from start to end.
That's right.
I worked on "Modern Boy" for a brief time.
Even though all the scenes were edited out,
I dubbed...
You were completely edited out? You didn't appear?
I don't think I appeared.
(Even the dubbed voice was edited out.)
Not even one scene?
I couldn't find myself.
They edited so many scenes out.
(He failed to leave because of the bag.)
The director kept avoiding my eyes.
- He avoided mine as well.
- What?
Why did he avoid your eyes?
I auditioned for "Happy End" and failed.
We share a common pain.
- We share a common pain.
- Don't put me there.
(The man shows up on his own.)
Really?
- Great work today.
- Are you leaving?
(Director Jung Ji Woo came to greet them.)
- Yes. Great work.
- See you later.
Have a cup of coffee before you go.
- Pardon?
- Yes. Have a cup of coffee.
Why are you avoiding Kwang Kyu?
I heard you completely edited him out.
- No...
- Where are you going?
(Kwang Kyu persistently goes after him.)
(Struggling)
(He successfully escaped.)
He really ran away.
Why did you mention that?
He wouldn't call me next time.
(While Victims 1 and 2 are feeling disappointed...)
(He got changed.)
Chang Wook. Have some coffee.
I want some coffee.
That's right.
Why are we clinking our glasses?
(My Star has to do interviews from now on.)
Cheers.
- To cheer you up.
- Hey.
You get no time to rest.
This doesn't have sugar.
(Barista Kwang Kyu feels proud too.)
(When things are busy and hectic,)
(caffeine is the best.)
You have to get going now.
(Back to work after a sweet break)
(My Star's Schedule)
(1pm, Interview shoot 1)
(Private Shoot)
We shouldn't be filming this, right?
Let's stay in our room.
(Heading to the waiting room due to a private interview issue)
Why does he have interviews nonstop?
(My Star went into a 3-hour interview.)
(While My Star is in his private interview...)
(They go outside with their hands full.)
- This is Cheonggyecheon Stream.
- What?
It's Cheonggyecheon Stream.
Is it the Cheonggyecheon Stream flowing below?
- That's right.
- It's Cheonggyecheon Stream.
(They see Cheonggyecheon Stream as soon as they step out.)
Shall we just walk along Cheonggyecheon Stream?
- You've never been to it, right?
- Right.
Look at this city boy.
I've been to Cheonggyecheon Stream like two times.
I'm in trouble.
(What are those?)
My head feels hot.
They asked you to promote it to people on the street.
- What?
- Promote it to the public.
(The request for street promotion?)
Are you taking them all?
- Yes.
- Who's going to carry them?
On September 18, "The Scandal" will launch at 5pm...
At 5pm?
Yes, at 5pm.
If you walk just a bit, there's Dongdaemun Market.
We can go to Migliore or Doota.
We can buy clothes for fall...
and give it out to the store owners.
- To promote in person?
- Yes.
(They'll even promote it in person.)
How are you going to promote it to people from abroad?
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Welcome. Come on.
It's an OTT drama, "The Scandal."
Yes. May 18.
(In Korean)
What?
- May 18.
- September 18.
- September.
- May 18.
Oh, September 18.
Do you know me? Hi. Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
- Yes.
- Welcome to Korea.
- Bye.
- Thank you. Bye.
- September 18.
- It starts at 5pm.
- Yes.
Okay.
(Leave the English conversation to the Genie.)
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
(What he knows in English)
Why don't we promote it to people from abroad?
- Sounds good.
- What?
Since it's a global drama, let's promote it to foreigners.
There are many foreigners in Dongdaemun.
- That's right.
- Right?
People from abroad might not know.
It's only right to promote it to people from abroad.
I've worked as a salesman for a long time.
For example, in fashion.
First of all, you have to be shameless.
You can't be shy.
Approach them with confidence.
Start a conversation with confidence.
How shameless do you have to be...
to talk to foreigners in Korean?
That's how shameless you have to be.
So we can communicate and promote the series.
That's the spirit you need.
(The shameless promotion secretary is ready.)
Anyway, it's too hot.
It's Cheonggyecheon Stream.
- It's nice, isn't it?
- Yes.
(The Seoul hillbilly in Cheonggyecheon Stream)
(Intrigued)
- Kwang Kyu.
- Yes?
That carp is so big.
- Oh, that's huge.
- Right?
I didn't know it could get that big.
Are there supposed to be carp?
(Taking a walk in Cheonggyecheon Stream)
That's big.
That's really big. Amazing.
I used to come here a lot 20 years ago.
Check out the cloud in the sky.
It looks strange.
Hey, isn't that a rainbow?
(Getting sentimental)
How can there be a rainbow without rain?
Up there. Look.
(Seo Jin's being too realistic.)
It's nice.
How can you be so amazed...
by Dongdaemun when you live in Seoul?
- It...
- What?
It'd be nice to check out Cheonggyecheon Stream.
Hello.
I'm a fan of My Genie Secretary.
Thank you.
I should give her one...
since she says she's a fan.
On OTT on May 18.
- "The Scandal" at 5pm.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Kwang Kyu, it's September.
September 18. I keep saying May.
It's this month.
It's at 5pm, right?
(On September 18, "The Scandal" will launch at 5pm.)
Next Friday.
(He's shameless, but he doesn't have a good memory.)
Kids.
- Hello.
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
- Read it out loud.
- "The Scandal."
- On OTT.
Again. Go.
- "The Scandal" on OTT.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
But it's R-rated.
Hey. Give it back.
- It's...
- It's okay. Give it to them.
Okay.
Anyway, tell your parents.
- Okay.
- "The Scandal."
What does your father do?
(Being fan-friendly)
Okay. Bye.
- Say he's a gang.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Hey.
- Let's go inside.
Is it R-rated?
I guess so.
Do we need to get permission to film inside?
Do you have any connection here?
I know the chairman.
Can you talk to the chairman?
(The Young Master is new to Dongdaemun,)
(but he knows the chairman.)
I've met the chairman before too.
(Filmed with the permission in a hurry)
- It's nice. It's so nice.
- What?
It's changed so much.
It's quite different from the past.
(The building changed a lot compared to 30 years ago.)
(Spotting a foreigner)
There's a foreigner.
- Hi. Hello.
- Hello.
It's the OTT series. Understand?
Yes.
Saturday, September 18...
(Unable to communicate)
Friday at 5pm...
- Is he talking in Korean again?
- Where did Seo Jin go?
(Seo Jin, help.)
My goodness.
I can't say September 18.
- September 18.
- Yes.
It starts at 5pm.
- On OTT. "The Scandal."
- On OTT. Okay.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
(Promoting the series in English with his sexy smile)
- Okay. Thank you.
- Okay.
It's a tumbler from the OTT platform. It's a gift.
- Thank you very much.
- Yes.
Nice...
- Have a nice day.
- Thank you. You too.
Yes. Thank you.
You shouldn't speak Korean to foreigners.
Because of the movie "The Scandal..."
in Korea...
Thank you.
(Filming the interview with global press)
- Hello. To all fans in...
- Cue.
Are you all enjoying watching this?
If you're curious,
go over the fence.
Actually...
It's quite hectic.
Regardless of the secretaries or whatever.
With the interview stuck in my head and all.
(In the meantime, the secretaries...)
(Pause)
(Entering the store after spotting something)
The Young Master finally...
(Staring)
Which one?
I wonder if you can pull it off.
- Which one?
- Hello.
(What are you wearing?)
(Seo Genie's been paying attention to the older bestie.)
(He made a comment on Kwang Kyu's fashion...)
(every time they met.)
(His groundbreaking fashion philosophy)
(Fashionable Seo Genie tries styling his older bestie.)
These are super wide, right?
They might be nice to wear.
This is similar to the pants you're wearing.
- Really?
- About that wide.
- What do you think?
- Wide pants?
- Yes.
- They come in two colours.
- Aren't they women's?
- No.
Is your size 30 or 32?
- Size 32...
- Isn't your size 34?
- Thirty...
- Be honest.
Do you have size 33?
- Rather than this?
- How about these with that?
What? Rather than this?
How about these with that?
(Seo Genie's choice)
I like the sweater next to it better.
No.
(He has a quite bold taste.)
With that. Top and bottom.
- The shirt?
- Yes.
(A blue shirt with wide slacks)
(He likes neither.)
The shirt too.
- Can I try this on?
- No.
- I'm attracted to this.
(He has the worst taste ever.)
Hang on. I'll pick the T-shirt for you.
He needs to dress luxuriously.
At least his clothes need to look luxurious.
But he keeps eyeing...
those kinds.
That's only for young people.
If he wears that, he's over.
It'd look like something he's worn...
for a long time.
Hey. You should get one too.
No, I'm okay.
- Let's...
- Don't worry about me.
- Are you sure?
- Don't mind me.
We need to start going.
- Really?
- He'll be done after that.
(What's the result of Seo Genie's older bestie's makeover?)
He can't pull them off if they're too wide.
(He looks quite pitiful.)
We don't have time.
We have enough time.
- But this is...
- Kwang Kyu, you look good.
But it's so awkward.
I look like an old man.
These are flares.
(Rolling up the sleeves)
Right?
(Seo Jin will also style him.)
People would wear something this wide?
What do you think? Isn't it nice?
- It's nice.
- Not bad.
Because he's from a rich family, he knew what to wear.
He has a good sense of fashion.
(Seo Genie is a fashionista.)
It's my habit.
I have a habit...
of dressing people up.
It's not because I'm warm-hearted.
(Coy)
So they look nice to my eyes.
(For his eyes to enjoy)
You think so?
Kwang Kyu, you look different.
- But the pants...
- What?
Not bad, right?
- We have to go now.
- What?
He never dressed like that before.
It's nice.
Excuse me. We're ready to pay.
- Are you paying?
- Yes.
I could pay for them myself.
Done?
These are comfortable, though.
(Happy)
You are Ji Chang Wook.
(Becoming Ji Chang Wook's lookalike)
The Young Master bought me clothes...
for Chuseok.
Are you sure about this?
My goodness.
(On their way to meet My Star after his makeover)
(Waiting in front of the interview venue)
(My Star completed one more interview.)
Chang Wook, he got changed...
just like you.
(How do I look?)
Wait a minute.
Nice to meet you.
(Flustered to see his secretary looking like him)
If you're too tired, I'll be your replacement.
I'm Ji Chang Wook.
When did you get changed?
For My Star,
I prepared several styles of outfits.
- Let's go up.
- Let's go.
(Staring)
You don't look good.
- Me?
- You must be tired.
- I'm starting to...
- What?
I'm starting to get tired.
You don't look as good as before.
You need to eat something.
(Press conference and interview for 5 hours straight)
(But he has another interview.)
(My Star goes in for another interview.)
(It's been 7 hours since he began working.)
He spends this many hours on promotion?
I see why he's a global star.
I've never seen doing so many interviews...
since early in the morning.
He works so hard.
He has no breaks.
He's working so hard.
No wonder he gets burned out.
(This is how his day goes.)
(At 9am, arriving)
(At 9:30am, interview)
(At 11am, press conference)
(At 1pm, another interview)
(At 2pm, filming promotion content)
(At 3pm, interview)
(At 3pm, endless interviews)
(At 4pm, endless interviews)
- Bye.
(At 5pm, filming promotion content)
"The Scandal" on OTT.
Don't miss it.
(Chang Wook's schedule ends.)
Good work.
- Good work.
(Polite)
He's coming.
(The secretaries are waiting for My Star.)
Good work.
- Good work.
- Thank you.
He couldn't even talk to her.
I couldn't.
Hi.
- She's too...
- Your replacement is waiting.
Your replacement.
I'm done for the day.
Good job.
Well done.
She's leaving.
- Where?
- Nana.
(Nana?)
- Good work.
- Good job.
- Are you done?
No, only this conference is over. Our work is not over yet.
- Nana, how about a picture?
- Okay.
Here.
- Why...
- No.
I'm standing right next to you too.
- Why not take a picture with me?
- Take a picture of us.
Come to the center.
Me in the center?
You should be in the center.
(Seo Genie becomes a photographer.)
- He's doing his best.
- Yaho.
Yaho.
(Between My Star and the real My Star)
Do you want to see this first, Chang Wook?
- Right.
- What's this?
It's from your fan.
There's also a letter.
(While promoting in person,)
(they ran into My Star's fans.)
(My Star's fans from Hong Kong)
(Obtaining a handwritten letter and a gift)
(My Star is indeed a global star.)
That's from your fan from Hong Kong.
It's from Young Cheon.
(My global Star)
- Is it in Korean?
- Yes, in Korean.
(Touched)
Thank you so much.
Why are you thanking us?
(They only did their job as secretaries.)
I also have a gift for you.
(A gift for us?)
I have a gift for you.
It's been there for a while. They're for us?
It's been here for a while. They're for you.
(Vacuum)
It's...
(Expectant)
It's the wet and dry vacuum.
So...
it features ultra-high temperature...
direct steam spray.
- Really?
- The guests...
The guests should give us gifts...
to encourage us.
(Now he finally feels like working.)
That's nice.
- I wanted to get you something.
- I'm actually moving,
and I need to clean my new place.
Oh, really?
- It's perfect timing.
That's perfect.
(Learning how to use the gift)
- This is it.
- This is it?
- There it is.
- It's spraying.
(Getting rid of the smell by spraying)
The spray...
also gets rid of the smell.
The brush will clean the floor...
with hot water.
It'll get rid of the oil stain.
It's clean now.
- That's interesting.
- Okay.
(Thank you, My Star.)
Are we going to take four-cut photos?
Of course. Anything you say.
(My Star's healing time, anything you want.)
What do you do on your day off?
Anything you like to do?
I only exercise.
- You exercise?
- Yes.
(Seo Jin exercises 3 hours when he's off.)
Jogging is popular these days.
But it's not easy...
for me to join a crew.
- Why not?
- Or a group.
Why not?
I feel like people shouldn't group together.
I hate gathering in groups.
I hate exercising with a group.
So...
I'm kind of shy to join a running group.
- You'd prefer running by yourself.
- Yes.
So...
I always go hiking alone.
- I think it's important...
- I love it.
to have time alone.
I love it. It gives me time to think.
(Scratching)
It's fun to run together too.
- That's who you are.
- Yes.
Then you can run with other people.
- You like to be with others.
- Yes.
- You join clubs and stuff.
How many clubs did you join?
In the past,
- I was in a tango club.
- Tango?
A salsa club.
A cruciate ligament tear club.
Is that even real?
(Clubs are the vitamin of my life.)
The three of us should make a club.
A hiking club.
(The three of us should make a hiking club.)
What do you think?
- I just said I don't like clubs.
- Really?
(I just said I don't like clubs.)
I see.
I just said...
I like going hiking alone.
You two should live together.
(Sullen)
A club for people...
- who don't like clubs.
- That's right.
I just said I like going hiking alone.
That's ironic.
(I like any kind of club.)
I haven't been to this alley for so long.
It changed so much.
We're in the middle...
- of Rodeo Street.
- Yes.
I'm embarrassed.
I'm kind of shy.
(What are they doing in the middle of Gangnam?)
(In the previous season)
Did I...
get to do anything I wanted today?
(Did I get to do anything I wanted today?)
(My Star didn't get to do anything he wanted.)
(A preliminary meeting with the production crew)
Is there anything...
you want the secretaries to do for you?
How about...
taking four-cut photos with them?
I recently tried it with my friend. It was fun.
Or...
the claw machine was fun.
(Four-cut photo, the claw machine)
- It gives you a dopamine rush.
- Yes.
- I also like karaoke.
- Really?
But I don't think they're going to sing.
Kwang Kyu might do it.
He might do it if I ask him.
He might do it this time.
(My Star wants to make up for what he missed in the last season.)
(So the secretaries prepared the after-care service day.)
- Where's the four-cut photo?
- What?
Here?
(A customized after-care service for Chang Wook)
- The 4-cut photo first?
- The 4-cut photo?
Really? Sure. Sounds good.
I forgot to bring my hat.
This is...
(Excited)
I should've brought my hat.
Are we going in here?
(Excited to enter the booth)
Are we...
- going to put on a hat or anything?
- Let me see.
Any accessories?
- I need them.
- But...
- that's lame.
- You think so?
- Let's do it without them.
- Without them? Okay.
Wait.
Everyone in the photo.
(His face is handsome enough, so he doesn't need accessories.)
This one.
(The one who wanted to try it knows what to do.)
You've done this before, haven't you?
- Wait, that's... I do.
- You know what to do.
It's ready.
Let's back off.
Where? Here?
I'll sit down.
It's counting down.
Three, two, one. No.
(Genie will do anything for My Star.)
We'll do anything you say.
Really?
We do anything you say.
- Anything I say?
- Anything you say.
(All your wishes will come true today.)
Is it done?
- It's not taking a picture.
There's a remote.
Oh, right.
Seriously.
- We didn't...
- You said you've been here before.
- It just took a picture.
- Did it?
Where?
(Posing again)
Oh, no. My pants...
- What's wrong?
- My pants got caught.
No.
Hurry up.
All right.
What?
- You were too quick.
- Didn't you press it?
Did you press it?
(Will this be done before today?)
Hey, it's...
What's going on?
- You failed to take all the photos.
- Yes.
(Will they be able to do it this time?)
Oh, no. My face isn't in it.
(Oh, no. My face isn't in it.)
(Let's get at least one photo.)
Whose face?
(Moving to the back)
(To make his face look small)
(To look young)
(The secretaries are doing their best.)
- I look young.
- Okay. The seventh photo.
- The seventh photo.
- Here.
- What do we do?
(Quite proactive)
(Let My Star do whatever he wants today.)
- The last one.
- One last photo.
This is "yaho."
Yahoya.
I blinked.
What a big mess.
(The 3 are done taking the 4-cut photo.)
We have to choose.
(My Star picks the four photos.)
(The photo of them trying hard to look young)
Chang Wook didn't select the one where you covered your forehead.
The one covering my forehead... I'm hurt.
(The youth-chasing shot wasn't chosen.)
What's this?
- Gosh.
- It even provides a video.
If you scan the QR code...
- Do I scan the QR code?
- You can download the video.
- That's right.
- Then I'd better download it.
Why did my head turn out so big?
Your face looks bigger because of your lack of hair.
That's why I covered it, but Chang Wook eliminated it.
To my disappointment.
Should we stick one here? Like this.
Should we stick one?
- Because we have four?
- Yes.
All of them.
Only girls took one.
I can't find any with three guys in it.
There's ours now. Right here.
(We're here, My Genie Secretary.)
- Are we leaving?
- Let's go to the arcade.
- The claw machine.
- Let's play the claw machine.
(To the claw machine)
Gosh, there are a lot of your fans here.
(Chang Wook's second bucket list: Play claw machines)
What are we getting?
Which ones have you tried? Do one you're confident in.
- To be honest, I don't know.
- Okay.
(To My Star, the claw machine is...)
I heard you liked to play the claw machine.
Having played the claw machine for years...
- For years?
- Yes.
- You're an expert.
- Of course.
The key to winning a doll from claw machines is...
to play on one machine until you get it.
(Sticking to one spot until the doll comes out)
Try to get the bunny doll.
(A bunny doll)
And so...
(I'll show you right now...)
(why I'm the King of Claw Machines.)
(Claw machine skills honed through years of experience)
(The claw machine has its own dopamine rush.)
It's all about probability.
- That was good.
- Okay.
It was good. Here it goes.
You did it.
(You did it.)
(Will the King of Claw Machines succeed in one go?)
You did it.
(Dropped)
- See that?
- You saw that, right?
- Yes.
- The claw...
- let go by itself.
- Exactly.
The claw opened a little, right?
The claw opens automatically.
(Trying once again)
The claw let go.
The doll drops when it reaches the top from the shock.
Please take a shot of this.
(Upset)
(I've got my reputation as the King of Claw Machines.)
- Take a shot of it.
- Please.
Should we try the same machine seven times?
Go ahead. Try all seven times.
Let's see if you succeed at least once out of ten.
Continue.
(Focused)
(Sliding down)
(It's impossible.)
(Why can't I do it?)
The key to winning a doll from claw machines is...
to play on one machine until you get it.
I did it.
(Opening his eyes wider)
Continue.
(His fingers work faster.)
All good.
Get one.
(Sticking to one machine until it pays off)
I did it.
(It's not easy.)
It's tough.
- Are you done?
- Yes.
Come on.
(Embarrassed)
(Spinning the innocent stick)
What key? He didn't win any.
He didn't win any dolls.
- He was in the wrong.
- He was in the wrong?
Chang Wook talked as if he were good at it.
I thought...
he'd win a doll after ten tries.
How strange.
(Disappointed in many ways)
- Let's try something else.
- What's this?
- This one?
- The ten second one.
Ten second what?
You see the stopwatch?
For example, on your phone,
- you...
- Getting ten seconds?
You have to get 10.00 seconds.
This one's impossible.
(This one's impossible.)
(Hurt)
- Shall I try it?
- Go ahead.
- Getting it...
- Try it.
(Who dared to offend the King of Claw Machines?)
We can see the watch from here, right?
But how do you stop at exactly ten seconds?
- Tap it once, - Okay.
- and then again. So twice.
- I'll try.
Go.
- Two.
- I see.
- There's a stopwatch.
- See?
(Chang Wook has pressed the button.)
(He must stop at exactly 10 seconds.)
(A showdown with the King of Claw Machines' pride on the line)
(A tough, down-to-the-second battle against 10 seconds)
(Will they be able to experience the thrilling dopamine rush?)
(Success!)
(Succeeded on the first try)
What?
You did it.
You got it.
- The door is opening.
- Is it going to open?
The door is opening.
- It's open.
- What?
- For real?
(Finally getting that dopamine hit from winning a plushie)
(Secondhand dopamine)
In one go.
- What?
- Amazing.
How did I get it?
(Dumbfounded)
(He actually did it?)
Gosh, you're amazing.
- Gosh.
- How did you...
Unbelievable.
- I just got goosebumps.
- The honour...
You did it in one go.
- Let's go.
You don't need to try again.
- Oh, my.
- We got our money's worth.
- We did.
We got our money's worth. Let's go.
- He got the biggest plushie.
- Yes.
You have to stop when you've won something.
- True.
- Right?
- It's the perfect timing.
- Yes.
Stopping when you win something is...
- the right thing to do.
- It's a record.
It was totally unexpected.
I never witnessed anyone succeed.
I was genuinely surprised.
Some guys are just born lucky.
It was the best part of today.
That was the best I've felt lately. Because...
It was just hard to believe.
(Chang Wook miraculously stopped at 10.00 seconds on the 1st try.)
I paid to try the claw machine 11 times...
and failed all 11 times.
But to have gotten the prize on the 1st try out of 5?
It was an amazing feeling.
I realised why people play to win plushies.
(An explosion of dopamine)
My goodness. You'll soon be blessed with great luck,
stopping at 10 seconds in 1 go.
- Really, it's hard to believe.
- Gosh.
How did I win this?
(Moving to the next location)
- Goodness.
- What will you sing?
- You should sing first, My Star.
- Oh, my.
(Chang Wook's third bucket list: Coin karaoke)
You can't sing your own song.
- Can I not?
- No.
(Pre-emptively blocking Kwang Kyu's song)
Hold on.
Here it is.
- There's even the book.
- The remote control.
- You can search for a song.
- Yes.
Do you search from the book?
Yes, I do.
- I'm sorry.
- I search from the book.
- It was unconscious.
- I see.
- Do people not use the book?
- No.
Do they use the remote control?
Back in my day, we'd search through the book.
- You did?
- Yes. Go-to songs.
Then I will...
I'm going for Lee Moon Sae.
- Lee Moon Sae?
- Goodness.
- Lee Moon Sae's songs aren't easy.
- Lee Moon Sae.
Not many people know this song.
The song is called "You Don't Know."
- Don't you know - No.
Isn't that "Do You Know?"
(Kwang Kyu has no idea what it is.)
I don't know the song.
("You Don't Know" by Lee Moon Sae)
What?
(Staring gently)
The lyrics said he's looking,
- so I'm looking at you.
- What?
(Immersed)
(Sliding)
(Trying to act cool)
(But Kwang Kyu's actions bother him.)
(Mind you, it wasn't a video.)
(My Star's high-class singing)
(He's even good at singing.)
- Really.
- Gosh.
He sang a very difficult song.
The song was difficult,
- but the sound here is...
- Right.
very unforgiving.
- This is what I'm like...
- This kind of...
- I'll...
- when I sing.
You sang a very difficult song.
I'll accept the challenge and also sing...
Lee Moon Sae's song, "Blue Bird."
Challenge accepted with Lee Moon Sae's song, "Blue Bird."
Don't sing fast songs. You always fail to keep up with the beat.
I'm good at keeping the beat for this one. It's my go-to song.
- Is that so?
- Trust me on this one.
- "Blue Bird."
- "Blue Bird" by Lee Moon Sae.
"Blue Bird."
A moment that was too much for me?
Kwang Kyu's "Blue Bird."
When he handed me...
the remote to look up "Blue Bird,"
I gained...
some self-awareness.
I'm done for.
I came to my senses right then and there.
(Laughing)
Aren't I on My Genie Secretary?
(Weren't you going to take care of me fully?)
How exciting.
(That very song that made Kwang Kyu lose sight of his secretary duty)
Here I go!
(I'll have some faith in you this time.)
(My Star who used to sing by my ear)
(My Star who made my heart flutter)
(Its gentle fluttering wings were so beautiful)
(I always wanted to keep)
(My Ji by my side)
(Let go of the lingering sadness in your heart)
(It's a day passing by like a dream.)
(I'll try to be a little quicker on my feet,)
(so you won't hear the chirping of disappointment.)
(A heartfelt performance of atonement for neglecting his duties)
(Singing)
- Oh, my. Thank you.
- Safe. Thank you.
You sounded like you knew the song.
Thank you. I sang it numerous times.
- This is about as good as I am.
- Gosh.
- The song was nice.
- Right.
- Chirping - Yes, chirping.
(Chang Wook likes the song.)
Sing a song we might know, My Star.
- It's a showdown between the two.
- Yes.
Do you rarely sing, Seo Jin?
My throat hurts right now.
And I rarely sing.
(The dopamine crash)
All right.
- Which song?
- Kim Kwang Seok?
Which one? Which song?
"Love Has Gone." Can you sing it?
- "Love..."
- That's a high-pitched song.
Let's do "Love Has Gone."
Let's sing "The Parkingman of Love."
Why did Kim Kwang Kyu pop up out of nowhere?
- Kim Kwang Kyu...
- No.
- Kim Kwang...
- Stop.
- Kim Kwang Kyu is above...
- No, stop.
Kim Kwang Seok!
Kwang Seok, really.
(Well done cutting him off.)
("Love Has Gone" by Kim Kwang Seok)
This is a tough song, you know?
(Exploding with dopamine again)
(Even My Star's high notes are perfect.)
It's been a while since I've last had this feeling.
You know...
the feeling of getting tired while hanging out?
Something like that. How do I put it?
You want to hang out...
with your friends, so you meet up, but you're tired.
I see.
(I really wanted to hang out with them. But why am I this tired?)
- We played the claw machine, - It's a shame.
- took some photos, - But I'm tired.
- and even sang.
- Exactly.
But I can't dare to go home.
It's a shame, but I'm indeed tired.
- Are you?
- Yes.
(My Star, forever in pain because of their all-or-nothing personality)
It's been a while...
since I got exhausted just hanging out.
It can make me exhausted.
(My Genie Secretary-style after-care service is complete.)
- Are we done?
- Great work.
- My Star.
- A glass of wine is okay, right?
- Yes, I'm in.
(Digging in as soon as they sit down)
I heard this was your go-to place.
Listen. Here's the funny part.
I've only been here...
twice...
or something.
Is that so?
How is this your go-to place when it's only been twice?
- But...
- Yes?
- the owner...
treats me...
as a regular of this place.
- Because you're handsome.
- So...
I decided to think of myself as a regular.
(I might as well become a regular.)
You're busy anyway.
The owner must wonder when you'll come by.
Goodness.
After a shoot,
I wanted to grab some drinks with my friends.
But I didn't have much time because of the shoot the next day.
"Let's eat a lot, drink a lot, get drunk,"
"and go home within two hours."
Nice.
So we ordered glasses of beer,
chugged them down,
got drunk, and went home.
Let's make a club like that.
A one-hour club.
We just eat, drink for an hour,
and go home.
How about it?
(Read the room.)
Aren't you lonely?
Why do you keep bothering him when he hates it?
You two are both famous for having many kissing scenes.
Chang Wook, you're also famous for being an expert in kissing scenes.
(My Star, known as a master of kiss scenes)
You're known to make them look pretty too.
What's your secret behind it?
- The thing is...
- Must I be reborn again?
(Suddenly going off)
I'm sorry.
(Ji Chang Wook)
("The Adults' Real Love Begins")
(The top 3 most viewed are all kissing scenes.)
Is that the most viewed one? Is it 55.78 million?
- Is that Nam Ji Hyun?
- Views?
(55.78 million views)
Was it with Nam Ji Hyun?
The kiss scene with her must've been different.
(Let's admire the video with the most views.)
(A pro kisser!)
(Every Korean would've watched this at least once.)
(Ji Chang Wook goes all in during kissing scenes.)
(Ji Chang Wook's sharp nose got me hospitalized.)
(My heart can't stand his beauty.)
(I'm here to watch it again. I love you.)
(2nd most viewed video)
("Let me." What a crazy line.)
(Ha Ji Won)
(I became Ji Chang Wook's fan after watching "Empress Ki.")
(Expert kissers. How heartrending.)
(It's an old drama, but nothing is cheesy. Ji Chang Wook so handsome.)
Ha Ji Won was in "Empress Ki,"
- right?
- Yes.
Ji Won kissed with you too, didn't you?
No, we didn't.
- Did you not in "Damo?"
- No.
(Seo Jin and Ji Won were a couple in "Damo.")
So it ended with "Does it hurt?"
Old period dramas had no kissing scenes.
It was impossible with all the hair.
With the beard and all,
it'll get into the actress's mouth.
- It was impossible.
- Is that so?
Seo Jin, you have no strategy, do you?
In the past, all I focused on...
was making it look pretty.
During the millennium.
(Summoning the millennium)
But as the viewers' standards got higher,
they know when we fake-kiss.
For a kissing scene to come out pretty,
Yes, honestly...
it needs to be shot from many angles.
Yes, true.
You've got to kiss many times.
- Is that so?
- Kissing scenes are...
There's no method to making a kiss look good.
(There is no way to make a kiss look good?)
- But the roles looking good...
- Yes?
and the two roles' great chemistry...
(You must be handsome.)
can make it look nice.
Have you never developed feelings while shooting kissing scenes?
Kissing scenes aren't that romantic.
It's similar to action scenes.
(Kissing scenes are action scenes?)
- Do you agree?
- It's simply tiresome.
Do you agree?
Yes, I do.
Kissing scenes just drain you.
Do you agree? No.
I'm curious.
(The conclusion)
When shooting such scenes,
we go through many rehearsals.
(Kissing scenes)
Rehearsals.
Because the two of us need teamwork.
We have to work together.
How to move and such.
Right. Some scenes are shot at sunset.
- Correct.
- Yes.
- It's kind of...
- How do you know that...
without experience?
I've watched a ton of them.
(Ready for kissing scenes)
One day, I'll...
- You and me?
- No.
No, that's not what I meant.
It was a slip of the tongue.
I'll pray for you.
I'll pray that one day,
you're at the center of a romantic scene.
It was,
"I'll pray for you."
The "I'll pray for you" was in parentheses.
(I'll pray for you.)
- Thank you.
- Great.
Thank you. Well, that's...
By the way,
I heard from your manager that...
you only get ten days off a year...
because of too much work.
(10 days off out of the 365 days?)
You don't have any personal time.
- Ten days...
- Isn't it exhausting?
It's not ten days.
During one month,
when I'm really busy, I only get one day off.
- One day a month.
- One day a month?
Yes, 1 or 2 days off a month.
You've got good stamina.
Yes, I think I do.
But only these days.
You'd better have some wild ginseng.
You sometimes have...
drinks with friends on days off, right?
But these days,
I just sleep.
(I sleep.)
That means you're totally drained.
You're completely drained.
- You're just drained.
- So...
what I like most these days is...
falling asleep while playing Nintendo in bed...
after a good shower.
- Nintendo?
- Yes.
I feel bad for him.
I do.
Falling asleep while playing Nintendo on days off.
(My Global Star's simple pleasure)
That's...
the biggest happiness to him.
Happiness isn't something grand.
- You're happy, right?
- Yes.
- Good.
- As long as you're happy.
Cheers.
The works I've heard of are...
"Human X Gumiho" in progress...
and the one shot in Japan, right?
- Yes, "Merry Berry Love."
- That one too.
A special appearance in "The Generals."
- "Men of the Harem."
- You mentioned it earlier.
- I did.
All dramas...
- are being offered to Chang Wook.
- No.
Are you rejecting none offered to you?
- You still reject some, right?
- I'm curious.
- You see...
- You're rejecting some, right?
Listen.
At one point,
I decided to act as much as...
I wanted.
If you think about it,
in a way, I'm almost 40 years old.
There are roles I can take at my current age.
I want to do those roles as much as possible.
- It...
- Before it gets too late?
Yes. Regardless of the roles,
I want to do everything.
But not to the point of overdoing it.
You're greedy...
- when it comes to acting.
- I am.
I must still...
find acting fun.
- Personally...
- Yes?
You're 40 next year, right?
From what I see, 45 is...
when a guy's golden age ends.
(From experience)
You've done a handful of works...
- until now.
- True.
Until 45,
I hope you'll cut back on work...
and focus on your own life.
(How about cutting back on work and finding your life?)
I do think that's necessary.
Of course.
With that...
But there are only so many years...
of youth left.
Before it gets too late,
enjoy...
your youth.
(A life lesson from a senior to My Star)
- As expected.
- I think it's a good idea.
As expected. He's had his share.
I agree.
That gives you...
the time and space to think about life...
after 45.
(While taking a break)
Life of getting old.
(Life of getting old)
I've been thinking about that...
a lot lately.
These days,
I don't have a personal life.
It's all about work.
(A worry My Star has been carrying in his heart)
I think...
it's about time I had some...
- Of course.
- personal time.
Don't spend all your time working nonstop.
Take a short break.
It'll help you in many ways, like sorting out your thoughts.
(To be continued)
But it's you who makes the call.
(Obviously)
If you want to keep working, you do you.
- Right, of course.
- Yes.
If you suddenly...
don't feel like working anymore,
you might end up calling him...
for that club.
(Out of the blue)
"Kwang Kyu, I'd like to join a club."
"Which one should I start with?"
You might ask about starting a club.
Why don't the three meet up once every year?
For just an hour.
We'll eat, drink, and say goodbye in a flash...
without looking back.
But without asking for money or anything.
I'm worried about that.
You can't bring it up, okay?
(You can't bring it up, okay?)
We are an exception.
How come?
Come on, we have a special relationship.
(We have a special relationship.)
This time allowed me...
to clearly understand why...
My Star Ji Chang Wook is a global celebrity.
He worked from early morning...
and gave his all during the long interview...
without showing any signs of...
annoyance or anger.
Chang Wook kept smiling even though our show overlapped...
with his other schedule.
"No wonder he's a global celebrity."
In the midst of it,
he went live on social media...
and communicated with his fans.
We're done here. He could go home.
He has a shoot tomorrow. But he's staying behind,
humouring Seo Jin.
There's a reason...
he's a global celebrity.
Had it been Lee Seo Jin,
he would have left already.
(How was Thinker Seo Jin's advice?)
It was something...
I really needed these days.
The issue was something I should...
think about deeply.
It got me thinking.
My Genie Secretary is like...
a "Blue Bird" to me.
(My Genie Secretary is My Star's "Blue Bird.")
Great work.
Even though the bluebird has flown away
Chirping
(After years of being unknown,)
(RESCENE syndrome began with "Yaho!")
(The ultimate self-made idol...)
(who has coloured the whole world with RESCENE)
(Trendsetting My Star, RESCENE)
(They should be taking care of us oldies.)
(Yes, they should be taking care of us.)
(Average age: 56.5)
(Take care of RESCENE, average age 20.6.)
(The qualifications to become a manager of Gen Z RESCENE)
(Imitate "Yaho.")
(What's "Yaho?")
(What does your father do?)
(No idea what it is, but "Yaho" anyway)
(Do you know ParaPara?)
("Parapapa." Isn't it this?)
(That's "Zzarapapa.")
(No idea what it is, but dance anyway)
(Do you know the wax breaking ball?)
(Why is this trending?)
(No idea what it is, but destroy anyway)
(I should've done it with my members.)
(RESCENE suffer from the generation gap.)
(Jjyu walks too slowly.)
(Jjyu-Kkyu, where are our spoons?)
(Jjyu!)
(The secretaries suffer from Gen Z RESCENE's endless energy.)
(But the Genies do it all.)
(Starting with mosquito repellent)
(Make us laugh, Jjyu-Kkyu.)
(My Star-tailored laughter service)
(You gain happiness from earning lots of money.)
(But is money everything?)
(It's everything.)
(Even going as far as capitalist service for Gen Z)
(She's learned how capitalism works.)
(After bridging the generation gap,)
(they'll take care of RESCENE.)
(My Genie Secretary, special extended episode)
(A 17.9-year-old sings our song again.)
("The Ballad of Us 2" premiers on October 5 at 10pm.)